A very good evening to all the wonderful people gathered over here.
With immense pleasure and joy, I announce that today we are celebrating our very first annual day.
On this occasion, it's my honor to welcome the guests of the day.
My Chief guest, Mrs. Anjali Chaudhry-Partida, Director of Worldway International School,
Mrs. Poonam-Rizada, Principal of Worldway International School,
I also welcome other special guests of the day.
Mrs. Benzer Sayyid, Director of Little Millennium Hushangabad Road, Mr. Abhishek Corbu,
Director of Little Millennium Arirah Colony and Mrs. Ranjana Chaudhry,
Academic Coordinator for Little Millennium Bhopal Centers.
I extend a warm welcome to the parents and grandparents who are here today
to encourage us to deliver our best.
Thank you for being here.
As they say, coming together is a beginning, keeping together is progress,
and working together is success.
It was indeed this mantra of coming together that has brought us where we are today.
This is a very special year for us as we are completing the fifth year of our journey as a preschool,
and a lot has happened since then.
God has been really gracious to have chosen us as a channel to take care and nurture his most precious creation
and make sure that they be the most amazing human beings on this planet.
Also, this journey would have been unthinkable without the immense trust
and unwavering support from you all, the parent community,
who have been a part of Little Millennium Rohit Nagar at some point or the other since 2019.
I would like to take a moment to express my heartfelt gratitude to all of you.
Here, I would like to mention that life is not all about textbooks and bookish knowledge.
We need to learn many skills as well.
Anil function provides all the children with an excellent opportunity to learn practical life skills
such as confidence, public speaking, leadership, coordination, teamwork, and so on.
And these are the skills that will lead our children ahead in life.
Today's program is a collective effort of the entire team of Little Millennium Rohit Nagar.
Our super energetic children and their ever enthusiastic teachers have been practicing really hard
since almost a month to put their best foot forward on their annual day.
We are super proud of each one of them.
Let's give them a big round of applause.
Today, you will see the culmination of all the efforts that has gone into the execution of this program.
Another important fact that I wish to emphasize here today is that every child is unique
and should not be compared to another one.
All of our preschoolers are at a very tender age and most of them,
and for most of them, today's program will be their first formal performance on stage.
So, our biggest task today is to give them enormous appreciation, motivation, and applause.
Today's program will give you a variety of flavors from innocence to emotions, from bolivo and last, but not the least,
the unity and diversity of India.
So, ladies and gentlemen, sit back, fasten your seat belts and enjoy euphoria, a magical experience.